The Eichmann Show is a drama, history, tv movie film
directed by Paul Andrew Williams.
The behind-the-scenes true life story of a groundbreaking producer, Milton Fruchtman, and blacklisted TV director Leo Hurwitz who, overcoming enormous obstacles, set out to capture
the testimony of one of the war's most notorious Nazis, Adolf Eichmann, who is accused of executing the 'final solution' and organising the murder of 6 million Jews.
This is the extraordinary story of how the trial came to be
televised and the team that made it happen.
Leo Hurwitz, played by Anthony LaPaglia.
Milton Fruchtman, played by Martin Freeman.
Mrs Landau, played by Rebecca Front.
David Landor, played by Andy Nyman.
Yaakov Jonilowicz, played by Nicholas Woodeson.
Ron Huntsman, played by Ben Addis.
The Eichmann Show is a 2015 British BBC TV drama film produced by Laurence
Bowen and Ken Marshall and directed by Paul Andrew Williams.
It is based on the true story of how American TV producer Milton Fruchtman and blacklisted TV director Leo Hurwitz
came to broadcast the trial of one of World War II's most notorious Nazis, Adolf Eichmann, in 1961.
The film explores themes of nazi, press, trial.
The tone is emotional.